All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
It's been two years since the War of the Best in Marineford.
Scattered across the world, Luffy and his crew underwent special training to prepare for the trials ahead.
Now, thousands of feet below sea level, they set sail to the next step of their journey, Fishman Island.
Only by passing through its waters may they reach the New World.
Guys! Check it out! Over there! I think we made it!
Fishman Island! It's huge!
It's in a giant bubble! It looks like they have clouds! There must be air inside.
Whoa! Does that mean we're 10,000 meters deep now? It's not as scary as I thought!
All right! We made it!
Guys! We got company!
Well, crap. That's not good.
Sea monsters! Giant ones!
Aaaaaaah!
Go pose! That's how we're dead!
Wow! They look tough! I want one!
Wait! Is somebody riding them?
Landing at the Fishman Island! Beautiful mermaids!
Why would you allow these foolish humans to tell you what to do?
Crack him!
What the heck, Tsutome?
Seriously, we were almost there!
Forget about all that! Just hang on! Don't fall off the ship!
My eyes!
Mine too!
But I don't even have any!
I don't have any!
What the heck, Tsutome?
Seriously, we were almost there!
Forget about all that! Just hang on! Don't fall off the ship!
My eyes!
Mine too!
I don't even have any!
Oh, my God.
Whoa, it's like a whole circus of sea monsters!
You guys are the Straw Hat Pirates, aren't you?
So what if we are, pal?
Maybe you better tell us who you are first!
You have quite the reputation.
For starters, you were the ones who ruined the Arlong Pirates' plans.
That part makes sense at least.
But for some reason, two years back, when Hachi was in trouble, you stood up for your old enemy.
And then you clocked one of the Celestial Dragons right in his ugly face!
Fisher Tiger happened to do the exact same thing, and he's the hero of this entire island.
Fisher Tiger...
I'm not sure what to do with you.
Tell it to me straight.
Are you supposed to be our enemies or not?
How about I give you an option?
Enlist under our banner as members of the new Fishman Pirates, or else!
Or else meaning we sink you right now!
What'd you say?!
Fuel up, Frankie.
Hurry!
Huh?
You got a plan?
You and I both know that Luffy isn't gonna cooperate with these guys.
That we're 10,000 meters underwater right now, and if we try to fight them, we don't stand a chance of winning.
Especially not with those sea monsters!
So we have to go!
I need you to use all of the oxygen we have to make a giant coup de burst so we can charge straight into Fishman Island!
Whoa, are you kidding me?
We've come way too far... to die here.
I agree.
It's risky, but it's likely our only chance at surviving this.
If that's the case, I'm gonna fill it up right away!
Frankie!
Steer the ship!
Everything's gonna be just super!
Those humans are starting to look awful busy over there to me.
They might be up to something, don't you think?
Humans aren't that clever.
Whatever it is, we can deal with it.
So, have you decided if you want to be part of our crew, Straw Hat Luffy?
Yeah, right, you wish!
Stupid!
Huh?
Are you sure about that?
You did hear me say what will happen if you refuse, didn't you?
Guess you are the enemy of the Fishman!
Nothing but filthy human scum!
Why did I want to work for a big, dumb fish face like you?
Cut it out, Luffy!
You'll make him mad!
That's a real shame.
You won't be seeing Fishman Island after all.
Get ready to sink, Straw Hats!
Let's go!
See Lion!
All right, filled up and ready to move.
Frankie, you're up.
Roger!
Take them down!
Bring it on!
Frankie!
Let's go!
Hey, don't forget we got our own life!
Maybe we can fight some other time, all right?
Here goes...
...Cucupers!
Whoa! Look at him go!
Can't breathe! There's no more air!
I'm getting squeezed!
It's hard to breathe! And that's not just because I don't have lungs!
Hang on! We'll make it no matter what!
What in the hell? What's up with that crazy ship?
We're on our way in!
I'll be with you soon, beautiful mermaids!
We lost the conning! It got stuck when we crossed the bubble!
Look up there! What could it be?
This bubble! It's a double structure!
A normal ship would crash because there's nothing but air!
We're about to run into another bubble!
You guys ready?
Water?!
How do you go ahead?
This current is really strong!
Help me!
I can't breathe!
Crap! Four of us can't swim!
Come on!
Reach!
Nami! Robin!
Dammit! I can't resist the current!
That's one way to get in. Pretty reckless, though.
Well, we could still go in after them if you want to, Hammond. No way to know if they're alive or dead, though.
Yeah, let's track them down. We can't let Neptune's army get their hands on them first, now can we?
But before we do anything, we should go back to Noah and tell the boss what's up.
I think he'd want to know that the man who ruined Arlong's plan is here.
Maybe he's coming just there.
Who do you want to know?
I recommend that Spillyела ever mentions, leave such a road!
And that's close enough!
That's close enough!
That's close enough to clamps to collapse!
Take a look.
I'll look.
I won't.
Maybe I'll look.
Who cares if I look?
Now he's moving.
He moved.
No, he didn't.
He might have moved.
Who cares if he moved?
All right!
He's alive!
Thank goodness!
Where am I?
Oh, Luffy-chin!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
So how are you feeling?
Ugh!
Hey, it's Kami!
It's nice to see you!
Oh, Kami, you've got so lovely!
Marry me!
It's been two whole years, huh?
You haven't changed a bit.
Wait a minute.
If Kami's here...
We made it to Fishman Island after all?
Yeah, we did!
From what I understand, we were about to drown,
but then we were rescued by a bunch of mermaids!
That's right!
Sanji Chopper and I just woke up a few minutes ago.
Guess we're pretty lucky, huh?
Lucky enough to wake up in Kami's house.
Here, catch!
Oh!
So this is your house?
My bad!
I know I was supposed to pick you guys up on Saba Odi,
but I was thinking that was another month from now!
That's okay!
Where is everybody?
Well, uh...
It looks like we got separated.
Goodness, I hope they're safe.
So they're lost?
Yeah.
Before I blacked out, I was trying to follow them,
but that current must have pulled them off in a different direction.
Ah, gotcha!
Well, I'm sure it'll turn out okay, right?
They're fine.
The Bonehead can't do much underwater,
but the Robot and Mosshead are probably with them,
so I wouldn't worry.
Right, everything will be just fine.
I hope I get to see them again soon.
Anyway, here you go.
I'm sure you're all freezing,
so I made some soup that'll warm you right up.
Ta-da!
Cold seaweed soup!
It's yummy!
It's cold?
That's not right!
How are you supposed to get warm if the soup is cold?
I'm sorry!
What?
I'm such a failure!
Yeah!
But your soup is great, Kamey.
Yes.
I'm warmer already.
That doesn't make sense.
Come on, let me try some, too!
Your clothes are dry, everybody!
They're dry!
No, they're not dry!
Your clothes might be dry!
Who cares if they're dry?
Huh?
You keep care of our clothes, too?
Well, thanks!
Who are those little guys?
Oh, there's some friends of mine.
The Medica Mermaid Quintuplets.
I'm Ichika, I'm Nika, I'm Sanka, I'm Yonka, and I'm Yonka, too!
Wait, why are there two Yonkas?
They're really fast swimmers and pretty clever, as well.
Yeah?
Nice to meet you!
I've got a lot of neat friends here, actually.
This is the seafloor of the Mermaid Cove, home to the girls' dorm of the famous Mermaid Café!
Huh?
G-g-g-g-g-g-the girls' dorm?
Uh-oh!
Please, Kimi!
Tell me everything about this Mermaid Café, please!
Oh, it's just this cute little café where I work as a waitress.
We have a lot of pretty mermaids there on staff.
Ah!
Sounds like heaven!
Can I get you anything extra?
I swore I made a promise to myself that for the entire time I was on fish man island I
wouldn't get a nosebleed and pass out and I've held out for this long so I deserve a reward right
pathetic I know why don't we go up there now I'll introduce you to all of my friends
whoa a turtle sea turtle elevator huh could you give us a lift mr. turtle
this is a coral apartment complex the dorms are at the very bottom so rinse cheap
the top floor is the most expensive because it gets natural light hmm does
that mean you're poor and what about Hachi and Papa goop Hachin got beat up real
bad about a year ago oh yeah I heard about that he was protecting the city for us
back on Sabaody right Hachin came from the fish man district so that's where he's
been resting and recovering I haven't had the chance to see him lately but from
what I hear he's getting better all the time huh he's okay yeah but it's kind of
a rough part of town if you guys go along with me I wouldn't mind heading
over there to visit him though let's do it I've been wanting to thank him face to
face sure you got it and well as for Papa goo he's a super famous fashion designer so
he lives in a big fancy mansion in the high-class district officially hills I'm
supposed to deliver some clams over there today you want to come with me wait he's
your pet but you two don't live in the same place yeah cuz that area is a little out of
my price range we have better clams here anyway we're almost to the top huh hey what's that drinking
straw looking tube dealie oh that thing that's the water road the bubble craftsmen built it and
mermaids or fish get inside it well hold on here let me show you
it's the surface we made it
look I'm swimming in the sky
wait a sec if we're underwater why do we see a sky full of clouds
no way I don't get it but it sure is neat hey
Kami huh it's a girl where's that coming from
hey guys
whoa
are these your pirate friends I guess that means they didn't drown after all
you didn't come in through the entrance like you're supposed to so we were concerned
well hi there you're not as scary as I thought you'd be so you broke in that's pretty hot I kind
like a real life fairy tale a coral paradise a whole cone full of mermaids
I don't know what's the matter with Saiji now he didn't even cry this hard when he left the paratia
finally
I found my all blue after all these years
are you sure about that really
here let me introduce everybody that's Luffy chin he's the captain
yeah nice to meet you
Sachi chin is the cry baby the nose guy is Usap chin
that's me
and the raccoon is chopper chin
not again
oh why are you crying
come over here let's dance in the water together
okay I get it this is obviously too good to be true maybe I'm destined to die today
that's dark what the heck happened to you in the last two years to make you this gloomy
isn't this supposed to be the land of your dreams
ha ha ha ha ha you crack me up Zonji
I don't think he's joking
ha ha ha ha ha, that's the very scary thing
I'll be better-in version of the trick
Interesting.
So Straw Hat finally made it to our turf, did he?
Good for him.
Right.
Well, what are we going to do about it, boss?
I want you to bring him here.
And quickly.
After a safe, if explosive, arrival on Fishman Island,
the Straw Hats make their way to Mermaid's Cove,
where they receive a warm welcome.
Unfortunately, the three princes of the island
don't seem as cordial as the mermaids,
and the Straw Hats are forced to hide.
Then, just when it seems like danger is passing,
Sanji is struck with a shocking medical emergency.
On the next, One Piece, excitement blow out!
Sanji's life under threat!
I'm going to be king of the pirates!